On your home Xbox, anyone who signs in can play your downloaded games.
And if you have an Xbox Live Gold subscription, they'll share the benefits, too.
The first time you sign in on an Xbox One, if you choose No barriers
it saves your password and that console becomes your home Xbox.
If you were at a friend’s house when you first did that, their Xbox became your home Xbox.
But you can still change your home Xbox to your own console.
On the console you want as your home Xbox, go to Settings > All settings
Personalization > My home Xbox.
If this console isn’t currently your home Xbox, the description explains the benefits.
Press A to make the console your home Xbox.
If it already is, it says so right here.
Pressing A removes that console as your home Xbox.
You can have only one console as your home Xbox at a time,
but you can change it up to three times a year.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.